trollz.com 2017-12-30

# Privacy Policy - DHX Media

**_DHX MEDIA CORPORATE WEBSITE_**

 ** _PRIVACY & COOKIES POLICY_**

Last Updated: October 1, 2015 _._

Welcome! This Privacy & Cookies Policy governs the websites (including both mobile and online versions), online and mobile services ( _e.g._ , apps), and software made available by DHX Media Ltd. (“ **DHX Media** ”, “ **we** ” “ **our** ” or “ **us** ”), including your use of interactive features, widgets, plug-ins, applications, content, downloads and/or other services that we own and control and that post a link to this Privacy & Cookies Policy (collectively, the “ **Service** ”), regardless of how you access or use the Service, whether via computer, mobile device or otherwise. This Privacy & Cookies Policy does _not_ apply to data we receive from third parties, unless we combine such data with Personal Information (defined below) that we have ourselves collected under this Privacy & Cookies Policy. Subject to applicable law, this Privacy & Cookies Policy does _not_ apply to our data collection activities offline or otherwise outside of our Service (unless otherwise stated below), and does not govern the data practices of third parties that may interact with our Service.

To the extent we provide you notice on our Service of different or additional privacy policies or practices ( _e.g._ , at the point of our collection), those additional terms shall govern such data collection and use. Younger visitors should always check with their parents or guardians before entering information on any website or mobile application and we encourage families to discuss their household guidelines regarding the online sharing of information.

In addition, please review the Service’s **Terms of Use** , which governs your use of the Service. _By using our Service_ , _you consent to our Privacy & Cookies Policy and our Terms of Use and our collection, use and sharing of your information and data, and other activities, as described below_ _._ If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy & Cookies Policy, please do not provide us with any information and do not use this Service.

 ** _Privacy & Cookies Policy Table of Contents and Summary_**

 **It is important that you read and understand the entire Privacy & Cookies Policy before using the Service. To ease review, each section below contains a brief introductory summary and a link to the full explanation. Click on the headings and the “ _More_ ” buttons to be taken to the full explanation. Any capitalized terms that appear in but are not otherwise defined in the introduction have the meanings given to them elsewhere in the Privacy & Cookies Policy. **

  1. **_What Information Does the Service Collect?_**

We collect and receive certain information about you as you interact with our Service, explained further in this section.

(a) **_Information You Provide to Us_**

We may collect certain Personal Information and Demographic Information (defined below) that you provide to us  
when you interact with the Service. For example, we may collect this information through various forms and in  
various places on the Service, including when you sign-up for an account to use the Service or when you otherwise   
interact with the Service (such as when you view and click on activities) offered on the Service. _More_

(b) **_Information Collected and Stored As You Access and Use the Service_**

Certain information may be collected from you automatically when you access and use the Service. For example, we  
and third parties may use Tracking Technologies (defined below) to collect Usage Information (defined below) based   
on your Device Identifier (defined below) for a variety of purposes (including targeted ads), which may include   
tracking your activities over time and across third party web sites and locations. _More_

(c) **_Location-Based Information_**

When using our Service, we may obtain information about your location or provide other location based services to   
you. _More_

(d) **_Information Third Parties Provide About You_**

We may obtain information about you from third parties. _More_

(e) **_Interactions with Third-Party Services_**

If you interact with third-party services, those services may send us information about you and you or we may send   
them information about you. _More_

(f) **_California Do Not Track Disclosures_**

We do not look for or respond to “do not track” signals, but you may have certain other options regarding tracking  
and/or targeting. _More_

(g) **_Information You Provide About a Third Party_**

You may provide us information about others, such as when you send a friend or family member a message. If so,   
the information you provide (names, email addresses, etc.) may be used to facilitate the communication, but   
will not be used for other marketing purposes unless your friend or family member consents.You may be identified   
to the friend or family member in connection with such a message. _More_

  2. **_How Do We Use The Information Collected?_**

(a) **_Use of Information By Us_**

We use your Personal Information, Demographic Information and Usage Information for a variety of purposes detailed   
in this Section. _More_

(b) **_Use of Information For Recruitment Purposes_**

If you apply for a job with us, we use your application and related information for considering you for a position. _More_

  3. **_How and When Do We Share Information With Third Parties?_**

We may provide your information to third parties under various circumstances detailed in this Section. These may include:

(a) **_When You Request Information From or Provide Information to Third Parties_**

If you request information from third parties, request that we send information to third parties or interact with   
third-party web sites, ads, content or tools (including Facebook and other third party share functionality), we may   
share your information with such parties and/or they may collect your information directly. _More_

(b) **_Third Parties Providing Services on our Behalf_**

Our vendors may collect your information on our behalf or we may share it with them so that they may provide services   
to us and you.Some may offer you choices regarding the collection and use of your information. _More_

(c) **_To Protect the Rights of DHX and Others_**

There are a variety of administrative and legal reasons for which we may share some or all of your information. _More_

(d) **_Affiliates and Business Transfer_**

We may share your information with our affiliates and in the event of a sale, merger or similar transaction. _More_

(e) **_Co-branded Areas_**

Co-branded areas may include information collection by us and third parties. Such third parties privacy policies, not ours,  
govern their practices. _More_

(f) **_Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions_**

We collect and use information in connection with sweepstakes, contests and other promotions. _More_

(g) **_Your California Privacy Rights_**

California residents may request information about sharing of certain personal information with third parties for the third   
parties’ direct marketing purposes by contacting us using the methods described in this section. _More_

(h) **_Your European Privacy Rights_**

Certain European residents have certain data protection rights. _More_

  4. **_What About Information I Disclose Publicly or to Others?_**

(a) **_User Content and Public Information_**

Posting content in public areas makes it available to others. We may share and use your public information as further   
explained in this Privacy & Cookies Policy. _More_

(b) **_Name and Likeness_**

You grant us the right to use your name and likeness in connection with your posting and activities. _More_

  5. **_Ads and Information About You_**

We and third parties may send you targeted ads based on your location, information and/or behavior. If you object, you can   
exercise choices some third parties may offer. _More_

  6. **_Does Third-Party Content, Links to Third-Party Sites and/or Third-Party Apps appear on the Service?_**

We may allow you to access third-party content on the Service, or to link to third-party applications and locations from the   
Service, but we are not responsible for your interaction with third-party content, apps and locations. _More_

  7. **_How Do I Access, Update or Correct My Information, Communications Preferences and Questions?_**

You may access, update or correct your Personal Information and change your communications preferences as more fully   
detailed in this Section. _More_

You can contact us for more information about the manner in which we and our service providers collect, use, disclose and   
otherwise manage your Personal Information. _More_

  8. **_What About the Transfer of Information to Other Countries?_**

You consent to your data being transferred to Canada, the United States and the European Union. _More_

  9. **_What Should Parents Know About Children?_**

We recognize the need to provide further privacy protections with respect to personal information we may collect   
from children under the age of thirteen (13) and do not knowingly collect personal information from children on the   
Service that requires parental notice and consent under the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act without obtaining such   
parental consent. If you think we have, let us know. _More_

  10. **_What About Security?_**

No data security is absolute, but we endeavor to take reasonable steps to secure data appropriately. _More_

  11. **_What About Changes to the Privacy & Cookies Policy?_**

We may change this Privacy & Cookies Policy upon posting of a revised privacy & cookies policy. However, we will continue   
to treat your Personal Information under the terms of the privacy & cookies policy in effect when it was collected unless you   
otherwise consent. _More_

**_The Full Detailed Privacy & Cookies Policy_**

 **1.** **What Information Does the Service Collect?**

 **(a) Information You Provide to Us**

On the Service, we may ask you to provide us or our service providers with certain categories of information, such as: (1) personally identifiable information, which is information that could be used to identify you personally, such as your first and last name, phone number, credit card number, mailing address, username and password, birth date and email address (“ **Personal Information** ”); and (2) demographic information, such as information about your age and gender (“ **Demographic Information** ”). We may collect this information through various forms and in various places on the Service, including if you register for an account, through “contact us” forms, or when you otherwise interact with the Service. If we combine Demographic Information with the Personal Information we collect directly from you on the Service or the Demographic Information can otherwise be associated with you, we will treat the combined data as Personal Information under this Privacy & Cookies Policy. Where required by applicable law ( _e.g._ , in Europe), we will treat Demographic Information as Personal Information in any event.

 **(b) Information Collected and Stored As You Access and Use the Service**

In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you choose to submit to us via our Service, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) store or collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the Service (“ **Usage Information** ”). This Usage Information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies that may be downloaded to your personal computer, browser, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other device (a “ **Device** ”) whenever you visit or interact with our Service. To the extent we associate Usage Information with your Personal Information we collect directly from you on the Service or the Usage Information can otherwise be associated with you, we will treat it as Personal Information. Where required by applicable law ( _e.g._ , in Europe), we will treat Usage Information as Personal Information in any event.

This Usage Information may include:

  * your IP address, UDID or other unique identifier (“ **Device Identifier** ”). A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device used to access the Service, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier;
  * your Device functionality (including browser, operating system, hardware, mobile network information);
  * the areas within our Service that you visit and your activities there, including remembering you and your preferences;
  * your Device location;
  * your Device characteristics; and
  * certain other Device data, including the time of day, among other information.

We will use various methods and technologies to store or collect Usage Information (“ **Tracking Technologies** ”). Tracking Technologies may set, change, alter or modify settings or configurations on your Device. A few of the Tracking Technologies include, without limitation, the following:

 ** _Cookies_**. A cookie is a text file placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Service. A Flash cookie (or Locally Shared Object) is a text file placed on a Device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built-in to or downloaded by you to your Device. HTML5 cookies can be programmed through HTML5 local storage. Unlike Flash cookies, HTML5 cookies do not require a plug-in. “Regular” cookies may generally be disabled or removed by tools that are available as part of most commercial browsers, and in some but not all instances can be blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Each browser you use will need to be set separately and different browsers offer different functionality and options in this regard. Please refer to the help and support area on your browser for instructions on how to block or delete cookies. Note, these tools may not be effective with regard to Flash cookies or HTML5 cookies. For information on disabling Flash cookies, go to Adobe’s website [www.adobe.com](http://www.adobe.com/). For information on managing “regular” cookies, please go to [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/), or visit [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) (if you are resident in the E.U.), or visit [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) (if you are resident in the U.S.), or visit <http://youradchoices.ca/understanding-online-advertising#cookies> (if you are resident of Canada), which has further information about behavioural advertising and online privacy. Please be aware that if you disable or remove cookies, Flash cookies, or HTML5 cookies on your Device, some parts of our Service may not function properly, and that when you visit our Service your ability to limit cookies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.

 ** _Web Beacons_**. Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “1×1 GIFs”, “clear GIFs” or “pixels”) may be included in our Service’s pages and messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a page or email can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Service, to monitor how users navigate the Service, to count how many emails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular links were actually viewed.

 ** _Embedded Scripts_**. An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Service, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Service, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

 ** _Browser/Device Fingerprinting_**. Collection and analysis of information from your Device, including your operating system, plug-ins, system fonts and other data, for purposes of identification.

 ** _ETag, or entity tag_**. A feature of the cache in browsers. It is an opaque identifier assigned by a web server to a specific version of a resource found at a URL. If the resource content at that URL ever changes, a new and different ETag is assigned. Used in this manner ETags are a form of Device Identifier. ETag tracking may generate unique tracking values even where the consumer blocks HTTP, Flash, and/or HTML5 cookies.

 ** _Recognition Technologies_**. Technologies, including application of statistical probability to data sets, which attempt to recognize or make assumptions about users and devices ( _e.g._ , that a user of multiple devices is the same user).

We use Tracking Technologies for a variety of purposes, including:

 ** _Strictly Necessary_**. These cookies or other Tracking Technologies are essential in order to help you use and access our Service. The information collected by these cookies relate to the operation of our Services, for example website scripting language and security tokens to prevent fraudulent activity, improve security or allow you to make use of Service functionality.

 ** _Performance‑Related_**. These cookies or other Tracking Technologies are used to assess the performance of the Service, including as part of our analytic practices by third-party providers including Google Analytics, or otherwise to improve the content, ads, products or services offered through the Service. These cookies collect anonymous information about how you use the Service, for example which pages you visit most often, whether you receive any error messages, and how you arrived at our website.

 ** _Functionality‑Related_**. These cookies or other Tracking Technologies offer you enhanced functionality when accessing the Service, including identifying you when you use our Service or keeping track of your specified preferences, for example the country you visit our Service from, your language and the presentation of content on our Service (such as font size).

 ** _Targeting‑Related_**. These cookies or other Tracking Technologies to deliver content, including ads relevant to your interests on our Service and third‑party services based on how you interact with our advertisements and/or content and those of third-party services. This includes using cookies to understand the usefulness to you of the content and ads that have been delivered to you. These cookies are usually placed by third-party advertising networks.

There may be other Tracking Technologies now and later devised and used by us in connection with the Service. Further, Please note that third parties may use Tracking Technologies in connection with our Service, which may include the collection of information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services. See Section 5 below for more information on targeted ads. We do not control those Tracking Technologies and subject to applicable law, we are not responsible for them. However, you consent to potentially encountering third-party Tracking Technologies in connection with use of our Service and accept that our statements under this Privacy & Cookies Policy do not apply to the Tracking Technologies or practices of such third parties.

 **(c) Location-Based Information**

Our Service may use location-based services in order to locate you so we may verify your location, deliver you relevant content and ads based on your location as well as to share your location with our vendors as part of the location-based services we offer. You may be able to change the settings on your Device to prevent it from providing us with such information. You should consider the risks involved in disclosing your location information to other people.

 **(d) Information Third Parties Provide About You**

We may receive information about you from your friends and others that use the Service, such as when they submit content to us or post on the Service. Additionally, we may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect directly from you on our Service with outside records from third parties for various purposes, including to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities that may be of interest to you. To the extent we combine information we receive from those sources with Personal Information we collect on the Service, it will be treated as Personal Information and we will apply this Privacy & Cookies Policy to such combined information, unless we have disclosed otherwise.

 **(e)** **Interactions with Third-Party Services**

The Service may include functionality that allows certain kinds of interactions between the Service and a third-party web site or application. The use of this functionality may involve the third-party operator providing certain information, including Personal Information, to us. For example, when you register with the Service, you may have an option to use your Facebook, Twitter, Google or other account provided by a third-party site or application to facilitate the registration and log-in or transaction process on the Service, or otherwise link accounts. If we offer and you choose to use this functionality to access or use our Service, the third-party site or application may send Personal Information about you to us. Further, if you click on social media icons on the Service (such as for Facebook, Twitter or Instagram), those actions may be associated with, and we may have access to, your Personal Information you provided on those third-party sites or applications. If so, we will then treat it as Personal Information under this Privacy & Cookies Policy, since we are collecting it as a result of your accessing of and interaction on our Service.

In addition, we may provide third-party sites’ interfaces or links on the Service to facilitate your sending a communication from the Service. For example, we may use third parties to facilitate emails, tweets or Facebook postings.   
These third parties may retain any information used or provided in any such communications or other activities and these third parties’ practices are not subject to our Privacy & Cookies Policy. DHX may not control or have access to your communications through these third parties. Further, when you use third-party sites or services, you are using their services and not our services and they, not we, are responsible for their practices.

You should review the applicable third-party privacy policies before using such third-party tools on our Service.

 **(f) California Do Not Track Disclosures**

Various third parties are developing or have developed signals or other mechanisms for the expression of consumer choice regarding the collection of information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services ( _e.g._ , browser do not track signals). Currently, we do not monitor or take any action with respect to these signals or other mechanisms.

 **(g) Information You Provide About a Third Party**

You may request that we send someone else a communication from the Service on your behalf, such as sending an invitation to a friend or family member. You must have obtained the consent of your friend before making such submissions. The information you provide (names, email addresses, etc.) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used by us for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on our Service, your contact information, name or user name and message may be included in the communication sent to your addressee(s). Some of these tools may be third-party tools subject to third-party privacy policies.

 **2\. How Do We Use the Information Collected?**

 **(a) Use of Information** **by Us**.

We may use your Personal Information, Demographic Information or Usage Information that is subject to this Privacy & Cookies Policy:

  * to process transactions you request; or provide you with information such as to send you electronic newsletters or
  * to provide you with special offers or promotional and marketing materials on behalf of us or third parties, including to let you know about new products, services or upcoming events, where you have given us the appropriate permissions if required by applicable law;
  * to improve the Service, marketing endeavors or our Service offerings;
  * to customize your experience on the Service or to serve you specific content or ads that are relevant to you, including using your location information to display advertisements for businesses in your close vicinity, where you have given us the appropriate permissions if required by applicable law;
  * to place an order made through the Service;
  * to notify you of product recalls or providing other information concerning products you have purchased;
  * to provide customer support;
  * to contact you with regard to your use of the Service and, in our discretion, changes to the Service and/or Service’s policies;
  * to identify your product and Service preferences so that you can be informed of new or additional products, services and promotions;
  * to enable you to participate in a variety of the Service’s features such as to enable you to participate in online entry sweepstakes, contests or other promotions;
  * to improve the overall experience at the Service;
  * for internal business purposes; and
  * for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy & Cookies Policy.

 **(b)** **Use of Information for Recruitment Purposes**. Where you have provided us with Personal Information or Demographic Information as part of an online application for employment or internship, we may use that information in order to allow us to make an informed decision about whether to proceed with your application. We may, as part of this recruitment process, collect information about your education, employment history and similar matters in order to help us determine your suitability for employment. Where this Personal Information or Demographic Information is considered to be sensitive, U.S. residents expressly consent to our processing of this information for recruitment purposes by submitting it to us.

 **3\. How and When Do We Share Information with Third Parties?**

We may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregated user statistics, with third parties. We may share your Device Identifiers with third parties along with data related to you and your activities for the purposes identified in Section 2 above. Further, we may share your Personal Information with third parties such as our co-promotional partners or others with whom we have marketing or other relationships for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident, you have the right to request additional information about this sharing, so please see Section (3)(g) below. In addition, we may share the information we have collected about you, including Personal Information, as disclosed at the time you provide your information and as described below or otherwise in this Privacy & Cookies Policy. We may also disclose your information as follows:

 **(a) When You Request Information From or Provide Information to Third Parties**. You may be presented with an option on our Service to receive certain information and/or marketing offers directly from third parties or to have us send certain information to third parties or give them access to it. If you choose to do so, certain portions of your Personal Information and other information may be disclosed to such third parties and all information disclosed will be subject to the third-party privacy policies and practices of such third parties. In addition, third parties may store, collect or otherwise have access to your information when you interact with their Tracking Technologies, content, tools, apps or ads on our Service or link to them from our Service. This may include using third-party tools such as those of Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest or other third-party posting or content sharing tools and by so interacting you consent to such third party practices. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such third parties and, therefore, you should review such third-party privacy policies and practices of such third parties prior to requesting information from or otherwise interacting with them.

 **(b) Third Parties Providing Services on our Behalf**. We may use third-party vendors to perform certain services on behalf of us or the Service, such as: (i) to assist us in Service operations; (ii) to manage a database of customer information; (iii) hosting the Service; (iv) designing and/or operating the Service’s features; (v) tracking the Service’s activities and analytics; (vi) enabling us to send you special offers or perform other administrative services; and (vii) other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential. We may provide these vendors with access to user information, including Device Identifiers and Personal Information, they need in order to carry out the services they are performing for you or for us.

We do not authorize our service providers to use Personal Information for any purpose other than providing the services on our or your behalf. We may also use third-party analytics and other service providers to help us gather and analyze information about the areas that you visit on our websites in order to evaluate and improve the user experience and the convenience of our Service, and to help us evaluate some of the specific information related to your Service visits. Such third parties may set and access Tracking Technologies on your Device and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, potentially including Personal Information, about you. Subject to applicable law, we are not responsible for those third party technologies or activities arising out of them. However, some of these third parties may offer you certain choices regarding their practices, and information we have been informed of regarding such choices is available hereWe are not responsible for the effectiveness of or compliance with any third parties’ opt-out options.

 **(c) To Protect the Rights of DHX and Others**.

We may access, use, preserve, transfer and disclose your information (including Device Identifiers and Personal Information) to third parties: (i) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, subpoenas, governmental requests or legal process if in our good faith opinion such is required or permitted by law; (ii) to protect and/or defend the Service’s **Terms of Use** or other policies applicable to the Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (iii) to protect the safety, rights, property or security of the Service or any third party; and/or (iv) to detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. Further, we may use IP address or other Device Identifiers to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with third parties such as copyright owners, internet service providers, wireless service providers and/or law enforcement agencies, including disclosing such information to third parties, all in our discretion, subject to applicable law. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.

 **(d) Affiliates and Business Transfer**. We may share your information, including your Device Identifiers and Personal Information, Demographic Information and Usage Information with our parent, subsidiaries and affiliates. Subject to applicable law, we may disclose and transfer all such information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Service or applicable database; or (ii) in connection with a prospective or completed merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all or part of our interests and/or assets or other corporate change, including, during the course of any due diligence process.

 **(e) Co-branded Areas**. Certain areas of the Service may be provided to you in association with third parties (“ **Co-Branded Areas** ”), and may allow you to disclose Personal Information to them. Such Co-Branded Areas will identify the third party and indicate if they have a privacy policy that applies to their collection and use of your information. If you elect to register for products and/or services, communicate with such third parties or download their content or applications, at Co-Branded Areas, you may be providing your information to both us and the third party. Further, if you sign-in to a Co-Branded Area with a username and password obtained on the Service, your Personal Information may be disclosed to the identified third parties for that Co-Branded Area. We are not responsible for such third party’s data collection or practices and you should look to such third party privacy policies for more information.

 **(f)** **Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions**. We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (any, a “ **Promotion** ”) through the Service that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, allowing the sponsor of the Promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion’s official rules, such as on a winners list.

 **(g) Your California Privacy Rights**. We may elect to share information about you with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. California Civil Code § 1798.83 permits California residents who have supplied personal information (as defined in the law) to us to, under certain circumstances, request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

If this law applies to you, you may obtain the categories of personal information shared by us and the names and addresses of all third parties that received personal information for their direct marketing purposes from us during the immediately prior calendar year ( _e.g._ , requests made in 2015 will receive information about 2014 sharing activities). To make such a request, please provide sufficient information for us to determine if this applies to you, attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. To make such a request (limit one request per year), please send an email to: [privacy@dhxmedia.com](mailto:privacy@dhxmedia.com), with “California Privacy Rights” as the subject line or mail us a letter to: DHX Media Ltd., 1478 Queen Street, Halifax, Nova Scotia B3J 2H7 Canada. You must include your full name, email address, and postal address in your request.

 **(h)** **Your European Privacy Rights**. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (“ **EEA** ”) or Switzerland, you may have the right to ask us not to process certain of your personal data (or provide it to third parties to process) for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. Further, you can prevent such processing by indicating who you are and any contact information you have previously provided to us, asking us to cease processing your personal data and indicating your jurisdiction of residence, by contacting us in the following ways: Postal Mail: DHX Media Ltd., 1478 Queen Street, Halifax, Nova Scotia B3J 2H7 Canada; By e-mail: [privacy@dhxmedia.com](mailto:privacy@dhxmedia.com) .

 **4\. What About Information I Disclose Publicly or to Others?**

 **(a) User Content and Public Information**. The Service may permit you to submit ideas, photographs, user profiles, writings, music, video, audio recordings, computer graphics, pictures, data, information about your location, questions, comments, suggestions or other content including Personal Information (collectively, “ **User Content** ”). We or others may store, display, reproduce, publish, distribute or otherwise use User Content online or offline in any media or format (currently existing or hereafter developed) and may or may not attribute it to you. Others may have access to this User Content and may have the ability to share it with third parties. Please think carefully before deciding what information you share, including Personal Information, in connection with your User Content. Please note that DHX does not control who will have access to the information that you choose to make public, and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy or keep it secure. We are not responsible for the privacy or security of any information that you make publicly available on the Service or what others do with information you share with them on the Service. We are not responsible for the accuracy, use or misuse of any User Content that you disclose or receive from third parties through the Service.

 **(b) Name and Likeness**. We may also publish your name, voice, likeness and other Personal Information that is part of your User Content, and we may use the content, or any portion of the content, for advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities. For full terms and conditions regarding User Content you submit to the Service, please review our Service’s  
**Terms of Use**

 **5\. Ads and Information About You**

We and third parties such as network advertisers and ad exchanges may serve advertisements across the Internet and may use third party analytics service providers to evaluate and provide us and/or third parties with information about the use of these ads on third party sites and viewing of ads and of our content. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements, which may be based on your activities across the Internet and mobile media (“ **Behavioral Ads** ”). Behavioral Ads enable us to target advertisements to you for products and services in which we believe you might be interested. If you object to receiving Behavioral Ads from us on third party sites, you can learn more about your ability to limit Behavioral Ads below. Our third party ad network and exchange providers, the advertisers and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own technologies on your Device and track certain behavioral Usage Information via a Device Identifier. These third party technologies may be set to, among other things: (a) help deliver advertisements to you that you might be interested in; (b) prevent you from seeing the same advertisements; and (c) understand the usefulness of the advertisements that have been delivered to you. You acknowledge and agree that associated technology may access and use your Device and may set or change settings on your Device in connection with the associated operations. Note that any images (or any other parts of content) served by third parties in association with third-party ads or other content may serve as web beacons, which enable third parties to carry out the previously described activities.

Statements regarding our practices do not apply to the methods for collecting information used by these third parties or the use of the information that such third parties collect. We do however work with third parties to make efforts to have you provided with information on their practices and any available opportunity to exercise choice. The relevant third party’s terms of service, privacy policy, permissions, notices and choices should be reviewed regarding their collection, storage and sharing practices. We make no representations regarding the policies or practices of third party advertisers or advertising networks or exchanges or related third parties.

Some third parties may offer you certain choices regarding their practices, and information we have been informed of regarding such choices is available **here**

For further information on Behavioral Ads and what is known as “online behavioral advertising”, U.S. residents may wish to visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>, which provides information regarding this practice by Network Advertising Initiative (“ **NAI** ”) members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including the “opt-out” procedures of NAI members.

Opting out of one or more NAI members only means that those NAI members no longer will be allowed under their own rules to deliver Behavioral Ads to you, but does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different Device or change web browsers, your NAI opt-out may not, or may no longer, be effective. You may also opt-out of receiving Behavioral Ads on participating sites and services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance (“ **DAA** ”) website at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/#completed>. E.U. residents who wish to opt-out of receiving Behavioral Ads may do so by visiting [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). Canadian residents who wish to opt-out of receiving Behavioral Ads may do so by visiting <http://youradchoices.ca/choices>. We are not responsible for effectiveness of or compliance with any third parties’ opt-out options or programs.

 **6\. Does Third-Party Content, Links to Third-Party Sites, and/or Third-Party Apps appear on the Service?**

The Service may contain content, links or apps that are supplied by a third party, and those third parties may collect Usage Information and your Device Identifier when pages from the Service are served to you for their own commercial purposes. In addition, when you are on the Service you may be directed to other sites and apps that are operated and controlled by third parties that we do not control. We are not responsible for the data collection and privacy practices employed by any of these third parties or their sites or apps and they may be tracking you across multiple online services and may be sharing the results of that tracking with us and/or others.

These third parties may have their own terms of service, privacy policies or other policies and ask you to agree to the same. For example, if you “click” on a link, the “click” may take you off the Service onto a different location. These other online services may associate their Tracking Technologies with you, independently collect information about you, including Personal Information, and may or may not have their own published privacy policies.

We are not responsible for these third-party privacy policies or the practices of Third-Party Owners. Be sure to review any available policies before submitting any personally identifiable information to a third-party application or otherwise interacting with it and exercise caution in connection with these applications. We also encourage you to note when you leave our Service and to review the third-party privacy policies of all third-party locations and exercise caution in connection with them.

 **7\. How Do I Access, Update or Correct My Information, Communications Preferences and Questions?**

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information provided as part of registration. The Service may allow you to access, review, correct, update or delete Personal Information you have provided through the Service’s registration forms or otherwise by updating your Service account, and you may provide registration updates and changes by contacting us by email at: [communications@dhxmedia.com](mailto:communications@dhxmedia.com). In addition, depending on your jurisdiction, you may have the right to access all of your Personal Information in our custody and control, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law, and you may do so by contacting us as set forth below. If so, we will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable (but we may retain prior information as business records). Please note that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons.

When you edit your Personal Information or change your preferences on the Service, information that you remove may persist internally for DHX’s administrative purposes. You may cancel or modify our email marketing communications you receive from us by following the instructions contained within our promotional emails. This will not affect subsequent subscriptions and if your opt-out is limited to certain types of emails the opt-out will be so limited. Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your account or use of our Service, such as administrative and Service announcements and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you choose to opt-out from receiving our marketing communications.

If you have any questions or complaints about the Privacy & Cookies Policy or practices described in it (including the manner in which we or our service providers treat your information), you should contact us in the following ways: Postal Mail: DHX Media Ltd., 1478 Queen Street, Halifax, Nova Scotia B3J 2H7 Canada (Attn: Privacy Officer); Email: [privacy@dhxmedia.com](mailto:privacy@dhxmedia.com) _._

 **8.What About the Transfer of Information to Other Countries?**

Although DHX Media’s headquarters are located in Halifax, Canada, we have offices in the United States and the European Union. Thus, the Service is operated in Canada, the United States and the European Union and intended for users located in these jurisdictions. If you are located outside of the Canada or the U.S., please be aware that information we collect including Personal Information, will be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in Canada or the U.S. by DHX Media, its affiliates, and/or third party service providers. Also, please be aware that information we collect, including Personal Information, may be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in countries outside of Canada where the local governments, courts, government agencies and law enforcement authorities may be able to access that information. By using the Service or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing and storage of your information, including Personal Information, in Canada, the United States and/or the European Union as described in this Privacy & Cookies Policy.

 **9\. What Should Parents Know About Children?**

We understand the importance of protecting children’s privacy in the interactive world. We recognize the need to provide further privacy protections with respect to personal information we may collect from children under the age of thirteen (13) (“ **Child** ” or “ **Children** ”) and do not knowingly collect personal information from Children on our Services that require parental notice and consent under the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“ **COPPA** ”) without obtaining such parental consent.

Some of the features on our Service are “age-gated” so that they are not available for use by Children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from Children in connection with those features. When we intend to collect personal information from Children, we take additional steps to protect Children’s privacy, including:

  * Notifying parents about our information practices with regard to Children, including the types of personal information we may collect from Children, the uses to which we may put that information, and whether and with whom we may share that information.
  * In accordance with applicable law, obtaining consent from parents for the collection of personal information from their Children, or for sending information about our products and services directly to their Children.
  * Limiting our collection of personal information from Children to no more than is reasonably necessary to participate in an online activity.
  * If the Service is either directed to Children or we have actual knowledge that a user is a Child, the Child may be asked to provide his or her parent’s or guardian’s email address.
  * Giving parents access or the ability to request access to personal information we have collected from their Children and the ability to request that the personal information be changed or deleted.

In the event that we become aware that we have collected personal information from any Child without first having obtained parental consent, we will dispose of that information in accordance with COPPA and other applicable laws and regulations. If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your Child under the age of thirteen (13) has provided us with personal information without COPPA-required consent, please contact us at [privacy@dhxmedia.com](mailto:privacy@dhxmedia.com).

 **10\. What About Security?**

We endeavor to incorporate commercially reasonable, technical, physical and administrative safeguards to help protect and secure your Personal Information in our custody and control. However, no data transmission over the Internet, mobile networks, wireless transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and you use our Service and provide us with your information at your own risk.

 **11\. What About Changes to the Privacy & Cookies Policy?**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy & Cookies Policy at any time. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy & Cookies Policy and your use of our Service indicates your consent to the privacy policy posted at the time of use. However, we will not use your previously collected Personal Information in a manner materially different than represented at the time it was collected without your consent. To the extent any provision of this Privacy & Cookies Policy is found by a competent tribunal to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed to the extent necessary for the remainder to be valid and enforceable.

Copyright © 2015 DHX Media Ltd. All rights reserved.
